[
  {
    "question": "to take in; to absorb; to learn thoroughly",
    "correctAnswer": "assimilate"
  },
  {
    "question": "to soothe; to pacify; to ease the pain of; to relieve",
    "correctAnswer": "assuage"
  },
  {
    "question": "shrewd; keen in judgement",
    "correctAnswer": "astute"
  },
  {
    "question": "one who does not believe in the existence of any god or divine being",
    "correctAnswer": "atheist"
  },
  {
    "question": "gradual wearing away, weakening, or less; a natural or expected decrease in numbers or size",
    "correctAnswer": "attrition"
  },
  {
    "question": "boldness; reckless daring; impertinence",
    "correctAnswer": "audacity"
  },
  {
    "question": "to make bigger; to add to; to increase",
    "correctAnswer": "augment"
  },
  {
    "question": "favorable; promising; pointing to a good result",
    "correctAnswer": "auspicious"
  },
  {
    "question": "unadorned; stern; forbidding; without excess",
    "correctAnswer": "austere"
  },
  {
    "question": "ruling with absolute authority; extremely bossy",
    "correctAnswer": "autocratic"
  },

  {
    "question": "to come together as one; to fuse; to unite",
    "correctAnswer": "coalesce"
  },
  {
    "question": "to force someone to do or not to do something",
    "correctAnswer": "coerce"
  },
  {
    "question": "powerfully convincing",
    "correctAnswer": "cogent"
  },
  {
    "question": "dealing with how we know the world around us through our senses; mental",
    "correctAnswer": "cognitive"
  },
  {
    "question": "aware; conscious",
    "correctAnswer": "cognizant"
  },
  {
    "question": "holding together; making sense",
    "correctAnswer": "coherent"
  },
  {
    "question": "conversational; informal in language",
    "correctAnswer": "colloquial"
  },
  {
    "question": "conspiracy; secret cooperation",
    "correctAnswer": "collusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "equal; proportionate",
    "correctAnswer": "commensurate"
  },
  {
    "question": "forceful; causing to yield",
    "correctAnswer": "compelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "a summary; an abridgement",
    "correctAnswer": "compendium"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "disapproving; degrading",
    "correctAnswer": "derogatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "to dry out",
    "correctAnswer": "desiccate"
  },
  {
    "question": "extremely depressed; full of despair",
    "correctAnswer": "despondent"
  },
  {
    "question": "an absolute ruler; an autocrat",
    "correctAnswer": "despot"
  },
  {
    "question": "extrmely poor; utterly lacking",
    "correctAnswer": "destitute"
  },
  {
    "question": "without a plan or purpose; disconnected; random",
    "correctAnswer": "desultory"
  },
  {
    "question": "skillful; adroit",
    "correctAnswer": "dextrous"
  },
  {
    "question": "relating to discussions; relating to the rules and methods of reasoning; approaching truth in the middle of opposing extremes",
    "correctAnswer": "dialectical"
  },
  {
    "question": "an authoritative saying; an adage; a maxim; a proverb",
    "correctAnswer": "dictum"
  },
  {
    "question": "intended to teach; morally instrcutive; pedantic",
    "correctAnswer": "didactic"
  },
  {
    "question": "timied; lacking in self-confidence",
    "correctAnswer": "diffident"
  },
  {
    "question": "to stray from the main subject",
    "correctAnswer": "digress"
  },
  {
    "question": "someone with superficial knowledge of the arts; an amateur; a dabbler",
    "correctAnswer": "dilettante"
  },

  {
    "question": "a lie; something made up",
    "correctAnswer": "fabrication"
  },
  {
    "question": "humorous; not serious; clumsily humorous",
    "correctAnswer": "facetious"
  },
  {
    "question": "fluent; skillful in a superficial way; easy",
    "correctAnswer": "facile"
  },
  {
    "question": "a group, usually a small part of a larger group, united around some cause; disagreement within an organization",
    "correctAnswer": "faction"
  },
  {
    "question": "absurd; ludicrous",
    "correctAnswer": "farcical"
  },
  {
    "question": "meticulous; demanding; finicky",
    "correctAnswer": "fastidious"
  },
  {
    "question": "someone who believes that future events are already determined and that humans are powerless to change them",
    "correctAnswer": "fatalist"
  },
  {
    "question": "foolish; silly; idiotic",
    "correctAnswer": "fatuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "animals",
    "correctAnswer": "fauna"
  },
  {
    "question": "fertile; productive",
    "correctAnswer": "fecund"
  },

  {
    "question": "treacherous; sneaky",
    "correctAnswer": "insidious"
  },
  {
    "question": "to hint; to creep in",
    "correctAnswer": "insinuate"
  },
  {
    "question": "dull; bland; banal",
    "correctAnswer": "insipid"
  },
  {
    "question": "arrogant; insulting",
    "correctAnswer": "insolent"
  },
  {
    "question": "to provoke; to stir up",
    "correctAnswer": "instigate"
  },
  {
    "question": "like an island; isolated",
    "correctAnswer": "insular"
  },
  {
    "question": "a rebel; someone who revolts against a government",
    "correctAnswer": "insurgent"
  },
  {
    "question": "essential",
    "correctAnswer": "integral"
  },
  {
    "question": "to combine two or more things into a whole",
    "correctAnswer": "integrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "uncontrollable; stubborn; disobedient",
    "correctAnswer": "intractable"
  },
  {
    "question": "uncompromising; stubborn",
    "correctAnswer": "intransigent"
  }
]